I'll start off with my parents my
parents my my dad's a limp Olympian a
fencer representing China and my mom's a
gymnast a world champion gymnast
representing represented China
I started gymnastic when I was seven and
then I changed to Jim Nash from
gymnastics to fencing Junior World
ranked number 11
I was the Asian champion for 2011 musics
been always my you know my hobby because
I really gave me motivation to
everything everything else me like in
every perspective when I want to relax
when I want to get motivated to practice
harder and I think it was when I was 14
I was just messing in my computer and
there was this application called a
GarageBand I started there it's just
that as more as as more time that I
spent on music it just motivated me more
and more like I just feel like I really
actually really love music you know but
fencing I really wanted to continue on
but I was just telling myself at that
point is this something that I want to
do forever my parents thought I was
crazy they were really shocked when they
first heard me saying about this
audition they didn't know what's JYP
didn't know anything about like kpop I
was in a position where every parents
would like their sons or daughters to be
in you know good education good in sport
so after making this decision everyone
was just telling me like why are so
stupid why are you so dumb to make this
decision you have a bright future right
in front of me why why are you trying to
risk yourself it's a high highly risk
that you're gonna fail you are gonna
fail Jackson everyone was telling me
that even my parents at the beginning
and I came from from having everything
to having nothing I just thought to
myself like I know what I want and and I
I got it all planned out in my in my
mind other people like beside around
around me telling me stuff they're my
good friends but at the end of the day
they're not responsible for my life I
just believed and what I believed in and
I just carried on to do my own stuff
because I believe in it I just want to
ask if everyone if they're happy I mean
like are you happy because of your
salary the amount that you earn or are
you happy because you're the job that
you're doing if you think you're doing
something that you're like you're love
that go on this is your dream always be
hungry and what you want to do take risk
work hard and have no regrets
[Music]
you